<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>graph on LeetCode In The Shell</title>
    <link>//alfmunny.com/leetcode-blog/tags/graph/</link>
    <description>Recent content in graph on LeetCode In The Shell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 20:45:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//alfmunny.com/leetcode-blog/tags/graph/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>210 - Course Schedule II</title>
      <link>//alfmunny.com/leetcode-blog/posts/210-course-schedule-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 20:45:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//alfmunny.com/leetcode-blog/posts/210-course-schedule-ii/</guid>
      <description>leetcode
Problem There are a total of n courses you have to take, labeled from 0 to n-1. Some courses may have prerequisites, for example to take course 0 you have to first take course 1, which is expressed as a pair: [0,1] Given the total number of courses and a list of prerequisite pairs, return the ordering of courses you should take to finish all courses. There may be multiple correct orders, you just need to return one of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>207 - Course Schedule</title>
      <link>//alfmunny.com/leetcode-blog/posts/207-course-schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 19:57:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//alfmunny.com/leetcode-blog/posts/207-course-schedule/</guid>
      <description>leetcode
Problem There are a total of numCourses courses you have to take, labeled from 0 to numCourses-1. Some courses may have prerequisites, for example to take course 0 you have to first take course 1, which is expressed as a pair: [0,1] Given the total number of courses and a list of prerequisite pairs, is it possible for you to finish all courses? Example 1: Input: numCourses = 2, prerequisites = [[1,0]] Output: true Explanation: There are a total of 2 courses to take.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>886 - Possible Bipartition</title>
      <link>//alfmunny.com/leetcode-blog/posts/886-possible-bipartition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 16:37:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//alfmunny.com/leetcode-blog/posts/886-possible-bipartition/</guid>
      <description>leetcode
Problem Given a set of N people (numbered 1, 2, ..., N), we would like to split everyone into two groups of any size. Each person may dislike some other people, and they should not go into the same group. Formally, if dislikes[i] = [a, b], it means it is not allowed to put the people numbered a and b into the same group. Return true if and only if it is possible to split everyone into two groups in this way.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>